Herman Wolf Papers 1985.0008
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series X: National Politics, undated, 1933-1976
  - 1968
    - Nixon, Richard
      - Republican National Committee: republican outlook (Box 24)
    - Ronald Reagan for President Committee (Box 24)
    - Wallace, George
      - Press clippings (Box 24)
      - Pamphlets (Box 24)
    - Gallup Poll index (Box 24)
    - LBJ and the Kennedys (Box 24)
    - Non-partisan materials (Box 24)
    - Saturday Review: "Nixon's Second Chance" (Box 24)
    - U. S. News and World Report: 1968 Election (Box 24)
  - 1969
    - Tax Reform Program (Box 24)
  - 1972
    - McGovern, George
      - Connecticut television (Box 24)
      - Connecticut television and radio (Box 24)
      - Connecticut visit (Box 24)
      - Democratic National Committee election materials (Box 24)
      - Million Member Club (Box 24)
    - Nixon, Richard
      - Nixon-Agnew Television Committee (Box 24)
      - Paulsen, Pat materials (Box 24)
      - National magazines (Box 24)
  - 1976
    - Carter, Jimmy
      - Connecticut visit (Box 24)
      - Election prediction by state (Box 24)
      - Inauguration (Box 24)
      - Campaign news clippings (Box 24)
      - Pamphlets (Box 24)
      - Pennsylvania Citizens for Carter (Box 24)
      - Speeches, interview, and writings (Box 24)
    - Ford, Gerald pamphlets (Box 24)
    - Official campaign ballot (Box 24)
    - New York Political campaigns (Box 74)
- Series XI: Personal Papers, undated, 1941-1981
  - Alaska Federation of Natives, undated, 1941-1981
    - Brochures, 1970 (Box 25)
    - Cartoon, 1970 (Box 25)
    - Campaign bumper stickers, 1970 (Box 25)
    - Campaign pamphlets, 1970 (Box 25)
    - Expense reports, 1970 (Box 25)
    - Federation footnotes, 1969 (Box 25)
    - Financing of projects and needs, 1970 (Box 25)
    - Land claims bill, 1969 (Box 25)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 25)
    - Natural resources and developmental trends, 1970 (Box 25)
    - Newspaper coverage: land claims bills, 1970 (Box 25)
    - Newspaper coverage: trans-Alaska pipeline, 1970 (Box 25)
    - Notes and memos, 1970 (Box 25)
    - Organization and structure of Alaska Federation of Natives, 1970 (Box 25)
    - Profiles of candidates (Box 25)
  - American Shakespeare Theatre
    - Advertising, 1962-1965
      - Companies (Box 26)
      - Newspaper bills (Box 26)
      - Plates and prints (Box 26)
      - Playbill rates (Box 26)
      - Radio (Box 26)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 26)
    - Festivals, 1964 (Box 26)
    - Finances, 1963-1965 (Box 26)
      - Bills (Box 26)
      - Budget (Box 26)
      - Cost Analysis (Box 26)
      - Publication Invoices (Box 26)
    - Memorabilia, 1964 (Box 26)
    - News clippings, 1962-1964 (Box 26)
    - Photos, undated (Box 26)
    - Publicity and promotion, 1962-1964 (Box 26)
      - Connecticut Assembly Resolution (Box 26)
      - The Shakespeare Guild (Box 26)
      - The Laurel Club (Box 26)
      - Ticket sales (Box 26)
      - Public Relations (Box 26)
      - World's Fair Show (Box 26)
    - Press releases, 1963-1964 (Box 26)
    - Student program, 1963-1964 (Box 26)
    - Stamp, 400th Anniversary Commemorative, 1964 (Box 26)
    - Theatre publications, 1962-1964 (Box 26)
    - Miscellaneous publications, 1963-1964 (Box 74)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 26)
  - Bridgeport Jets (Box 27)
    - Advisory Council, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Graphics, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Extras, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Newspaper ads, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Olympic buttons, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Photos, undated (Box 27)
    - Press clippings, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Press releases, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Programs, 1967 (Box 27)
    - Promotion memos, undated (Box 27)
    - Promotional plans, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Season tickets promotions, undated (Box 27)
  - General Correspondence
    - undated (Box 27)
    - 1944-1949 (Box 27)
    - 1950-1955 (Box 27)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 27)
    - 1962-1964 (Box 27)
    - 1964 (Box 27)
    - 1965 (Box 27)
    - 1966 (Box 27)
    - 1967 (Box 27)
    - 1968 (Box 27)
    - 1969 (Box 27)
    - 1970 (Box 27)
    - 1971 (Box 27)
    - 1972 (Box 27)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 27)
    - 1974 (Box 27)
    - 1976-1978 (Box 27)
    - 1980 (Box 27)
  - Labor
    - AFL structure (Box 28)
    - AFL-CIO candidate questionnaire (Box 28)
    - AFL-CIO Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1965-1966, 1972 (Box 28)
    - AFL-CIO state publication (Box 28)
    - AFL-CIO statement, 1965 (Box 28)
    - CIO expenses (Box 28)
    - CIO Political Action Committee, 1954 (Box 28)
    - COPE (Box 28)
    - CT State Labor Council (CSLC) (Box 28)
    - Greater Hartford Labor Council (Box 28)
    - IAM strike (1960), 1968 (Box 28)
    - International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, 1969 (Box 28)
    - Israel (Box 28)
    - Labor Defends America (Box 28)
    - Machinists (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous clippings (Box 28)
    - Morale Report on Labor, 1941 (Box 28)
    - Nations Business (Box 28)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 28)
    - Newsletters (Box 28)
    - Old plants/new plants (Box 28)
    - OSHA pamphlets (Box 28)
    - Pamphlets (Box 28)
    - Philip A. Randolph Institute, 1974 (Box 28)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham: speech (Box 28)
    - State Labor Department: AFL dinner, 1954 (Box 28)
    - Svirdoff, Mitchell: "Labor's Responsibility in Internal Union Affairs", 1959 (Box 28)
    - Taft-Hartley Act: A nationwide program to repeal Section 14B, 1965 (Box 28)
    - "Teamwork in Industry" (Box 28)
    - United Labor Committee (Box 28)
    - U.S. Department of Labor, 1960 (Box 28)
    - Wolf, Herman: notes (Box 28)
  - Subject Files
    - Allan, Foster, Ingersoll & Weber (Box 29)
    - American News Company, 1964 (Box 29)
    - American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publications, 1964 (Box 29)
    - Arthritis and Rheumatism Foundation of America, 1980-1981 (Box 29)
    - AVCO, 1966-1973 (Box 29)
    - Bolte Advertising Company (Box 29)
    - Bottle Bill, 1975-1976 (Box 29)
    - Candlewood Lane scandal, 1976-1977 (Box 29)
    - Carl Byoir & Associates, 1977 (Box 29)
    - Cattle breeding, 1968 (Box 29)
    - Census, 1961 (Box 29)
    - Civil rights manuscript (Box 29)
    - Communications Satellite Company, 1977 (Box 29)
    - Community (Box 29)
    - Compuval Company, 1971 (Box 29)
    - Connecticut Bankers Association, 1966 (Box 29)
    - Connecticut Flood Recovery Commission, 1955 (Box 29)
    - Connecticut Gasoline Retailers Association, 1977 (Box 29)
    - Connecticut Holiday (Box 29)
    - Connecticut Petroleum Council, 1959 (Box 29)
    - Connecticut Savings and Loan Association, 1977 (Box 29)
    - Doubleday, 1972 (Box 29)
    - Elsas Wolf Memorial (Box 74)
    - Ethics in Political Life Seminar (Box 29)
    - First Day covers, 1968 (Box 29)
    - Garvey Industries, Inc., 1970 (Box 29)
    - Genovese, Phillip, 1961 (Box 29)
    - Harconn Assoc. (Box 29)
    - Heublein Company, 1974 (Box 29)
    - Holy Name Central Catholic High School (Box 29)
    - Hotel Corporation of America, 1964 (Box 29)
    - Janeway, Eliot, 1966-1972 (Box 29)
    - Jewish New Year address (Box 29)
    - John F. Kennedy Memorial Library, 1964 (Box 29)
    - Kellems, Vivien, 1971 (Box 29)
    - King Cole stores, 1967-1969 (Box 29)
    - Koziem, Harvey, 1975-1976 (Box 29)
    - Kraut, Gary, 1969-1970 (Box 29)
    - Kupper, Kimball, Van Ausdall, Inc., 1965 (Box 29)
    - Leasco, 1969-1970 (Box 29)
    - Lists, 1968 (Box 29)
    - Memoranda, 1968 (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous transparencies (Box 71)
    - Monfort of Colorado, 1968 (Box 29)
    - Mooney, Ronald (Box 29)
    - Moore, Idella, 1961 (Box 29)
    - National Gallery of Art (Box 30)
    - National Spinning Company (Box 30)
    - Park Avenue Convalescent Home (Box 30)
    - Parsons, Barbara (Box 30)
    - Peter Paul Company (Box 30)
    - Pitzele, Merlyn, 1966 (Box 30)
    - Plant Environment (Box 30)
    - Public Affairs Consulting Executives (PACE) (Box 30)
    - Rosa Lea's Hotel, 1968-1971 (Box 30)
    - Schine, Leonard A., Esquire (Box 30)
    - Scientific Incineration Services, Inc. (Box 30)
    - Sears Island Refinery (Box 30)
    - Sikorsky (Box 30)
    - Small Business Administration, 1968-1969 (Box 30)
    - Sperry & Hutchinson (Box 30)
    - State police (Box 30)
    - Survey Associates (Box 30)
    - Texaco (Box 30)
    - University of Pensylvania (Box 30)
    - Van Doren, Mark (Box 30)
    - Vollmer Associates, 1965-1974 (Box 30)
    - Wachsman, David S., 1968 (Box 30)
    - Welch Design, 1978 (Box 30)
    - Wesleyan University, 1970 (Box 30)
    - Wilke, Philip (Box 30)
    - Wolf, Herman (Box 30)
    - Wolf, Irving Sr.: weight invention (Box 30)
    - World Review (Box 30)
- Series XII: Memorabilia, undated, 1936-1968
  - Ad: 7800 Workers Can't Be Moved, 1947 (Box 31)
  - Benton, William, 1950 (Box 31)
  - Campaign pins, 1940 (Box 31)
  - Congressional special, 1956 (Box 31)
  - Connecticut Citizen, 1950 February (Box 31)
  - Election flyers, 1950, 1951 (Box 31)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1950 (Box 31)
  - Lyford, 1954 (Box 31)
  - Non-partisan, undated (Box 31)
  - "Repeal the Sales Tax": Chester Bowles, 1948 (Box 31)
  - Ribicoff, Abraham, 1954, 1958 (Box 31)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1940 (Box 31)
  - St. Onge, William; Lamb, Gerry, undated (Box 31)
  - Stratford Election/Wolf State Representative, 1950 (Box 31)
  - "Vote Democratic" flyer, undated (Box 31)
  - Zeller, Fred, undated (Box 31)
  - Posters
    - Agnew, Spiro (Box 32)
    - Beck, Audrey (Box 32)
    - Carroll, Denny: congressman (Box 32)
    - Cotter, William: congressman (Box 32)
    - Daddario, Emilio: congressman (Box 32)
    - Dempsey, John: Governor (Box 32)
    - Kennedy, Robert F. (Box 32)
    - McCarthy, Eugene (Box 32)
    - McPadden, Wanda: state representative (Box 32)
    - St. Onge, William: congressman (Box 32)
    - Weicker, Lowell: Governor (Box 32)
    - Wolf, Herman (Box 32)
    - Bowles, Chester: Governor (Box 33)
    - Connecticut town politics (Box 34)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham (Box 35)
    - Grasso, Ella (Box 36)
  - Campaign Shopping Bags
    - Humphrey-Muskie, 1968 (Box 37)
    - Johnson-Humphrey, 1964 (Box 37)
    - Rockefeller, Goldwater, Stevenson, JFK (Box 37)
  - News Clippings
    - Chicago convention, 1968 (Box 38)
    - Campaign ideas (Box 38)
    - Election Day front pages, 1968 (Box 38)
    - Election Day aftermath, 1968 (Box 38)
    - Redevelopment news (Box 38)
    - Referendum ads, 1968 (Box 38)
    - Samples from each state, 1968 (Box 39)
    - Black press (Box 39)
    - Weeklies, 1968 (Box 39)
    - Thank-you ads, 1968 (Box 39)
    - National news, 1968 (Box 39)
    - Prete, John, West Haven, 1967 (Box 40)
    - Jepson, Alan, Milford, 1967 (Box 40)
    - Curran, Hugh, Mayor: Bridgeport, 1967 (Box 41)
    - Sullivan, John, Fairfield, 1967 (Box 42)
    - National and general news from CT papers, 1967 (Box 42)
    - State news, 1967 (Box 42)
    - Hartford news, 1967 (Box 42)
    - Political ads: local, state, national, 1968 (Box 43)
  - Senate races
    - Alabama - Arkansas, 1968 (Box 44)
    - California - Connecticut, 1968 (Box 45)
    - Florida - Mississippi, 1968 (Box 46)
    - Nevada - Oklahoma, 1968 (Box 47)
    - Oregon - Washington, 1968 (Box 48)
    - Samples from every state, 1968 (Box 49, Box 50)
  - Photographs
    - Jepson (Box 51)
    - Miscellaneous photos (Box 51)
    - Personal (Box 51)
    - Politicians: local Connecticut (Box 51)
    - St. Onge, William (Box 51)
    - Wolf, Herman (Box 51)
  - Buttons
    - Presidential candidates (Box 52)
    - State and congressional candidates (Box 53)
    - CT gubernatorial candidates (Box 53)
    - State and local candidates (Box 53)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 53)
  - Calendars (arranged by candidate) (Box 54)
  - Balloons (Box 54)
  - Key Chains (Box 54)
  - Nail files (Box 54)
  - Soda cans (Box 55)
  - Feather pen (Box 55)
  - Coin bank (Box 55)
  - Bumper stickers (Box 56)
  - Posters (Box 56)
  - Pamphlets (Box 56)
  - American presidency: calendars, posters, "special editions" (Box 57)
  - Personal memorabilia
    - Senate passes (Box 58)
    - Political autographs (Box 58)
    - Paper weights (Box 58)
    - Photographs (Box 58)
    - Date books (Box 58)
  - Ribicoff, Abraham memorabilia (Box 59)
  - Kennedy, John F. memorabilia, 1960-1963 (Box 60)
  - Dempsey votermobile guest book, 1966 (Box 61)
  - Newspapers and Magazines covering the Chicago Convention, 1968 (Box 62)
  - "Socialist Call" [fragile], 1935 (Box 63)
  - Political ads mock-ups, circa 1940 (Box 64)
  - War Bond art work, circa 1940 (Box 64)
  - Scrapbook (with copy), 1941 (Box 64)
  - Oversized memorabilia
    - Framed front page: Hartford Courant, 1962 November 2 (Box 67)
    - Scrapbook containing political news clippings, 1960 (Box 68)
- Series XIII: Publications, undated, 1940s-1969
  - AFL-CIO COPE, 1958-1969 (Box 65)
  - Committee/Department publications, 1967 (Box 65)
  - Communism, 1957 (Box 65)
  - Conference of Mayors: City Problems, 1969 (Box 65)
  - Conference on Economic Progress, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Connecticut Forest & Park Association: Connecticut Woodlands, 1969 (Box 65)
  - Connecticut Labor Department; news, 1967 (Box 65)
  - Democratic Congressional Campaign Manual, 1962 (Box 65)
  - Direct mail advertising, 1951 (Box 65)
  - Federal Government Outreach, circa 1940s (Box 65)
  - House Select Committee on Lobbying Activities: Hearings (Box 65)
  - Israel (Box 65)
  - Janeway Service, 1967 (Box 65)
  - Judaism guides, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Justice ILGWU, 1966 (Box 66)
  - Kiplinger Washington Letter, 1967 (Box 66)
  - Labor: general, 1958-1977 (Box 66)
  - The Machinist, 1967-1969 (Box 66)
  - Military Research: newsletters, 1967 (Box 66)
  - Public Relations Journal, 1969 (Box 66)
  - Report: Exemption of hospitals and medical services companies from state and local taxes, 1965 (Box 66)
- Series XIV: Audio-visual Materials, undated, 1950s-1975
  - Reel to reel audio
    - Aircheck of John Alsop and Horace Seeley Brown, 1962 (Box 69)
    - AH in Carbondale, 1971 (Box 69)
    - Caldwell for Senator (Box 69)
    - Citizens for Duffey (Box 69)
    - Congressman Olin Teag (Box 69)
    - Curran (2 reels) (Box 69)
    - Curran (2 reels) (Box 72)
    - Curran for Mayor, 1969 (Box 69)
    - John Dempsy - John Alsop debate, 1962 (Box 69)
    - John Dempsy - Gengras debate, 1966 (Box 69)
    - Duffey for Senator, 1970 (Box 69)
    - Ella Grasso Face the State, 1974 (Box 69)
    - Ella Grasso on Ch. 24 (Box 69)
    - Ella Grasso radio spots, 1974 (Box 69)
    - Kennedy Speech (3 reels), 1962 (Box 69)
    - Louise Wolf / Emilio Daddario (Box 69)
    - Mayor Curran, 1971 (Box 69)
    - Mayor Curran Speech, 1971 (Box 69)
    - McGovern, George (Box 69)
    - McLoughlin, 1972 (Box 69)
    - McLoughlin (7 reels) (Box 72)
    - McLoughlin for Congress (Box 69)
    - Abraham Ribicoff at Annual Meeting, 1962 (Box 69)
    - Abraham Ribicoff - Horace Seeley-Brown debate, 1962 (Box 69)
    - Abraham Ribicoff Lecture, 1962 (Box 69)
    - Abraham Ribicoff Speech (Box 69)
    - Abraham Ribicoff Telethon, 1962 (Box 69)
    - Senator Edmund Muskie and President Richard M. Nixon, 1970 (Box 69)
    - Stratford Democrats, 1973 (Box 69)
    - Harry Truman Press Conference, 1962 (Box 69)
    - Vivien Kellems and Abraham Ribicoff (Box 69)
    - 1962 Convention (7 reels) (Box 69)
    - 1968 Democratic State Convention (5 reels) (Box 69)
  - 16mm film reels
    - Governor (Box 70)
    - Daddario, Emilio (5 reels), 1970 (Box 70)
    - Oil's 100th Birthday (Box 70)
  - 16mm film reels
    - Campaign speech by Governor Lodge, 1954 (Box 71)
    - Curran, 1968 (Box 71)
    - Ella Grasso for Governor, 1970 (Box 71)
    - Governor Abraham Ribicoff Kinescope, 1958 (Box 71)
    - Kowalski (Box 71)
    - Mayor Lee (Box 71)
  - 8 mm film reels
    - Convention (Box 70)
    - Duffey for Senator (25 reels) (Box 72)
  - 6" and 12" videotape reels
    - Daddario (2 reels), 1970 (Box 70)
    - Duffey for Senator (Box 70)
    - Duffey for Senator (4 reels) (Box 72)
    - Duffey primary, 1970 (Box 70)
    - Frasinelli, Attilio (Box 70)
    - McGovern for President (Box 70)
    - Kennedy, Ted, 1970 (Box 70)
  - Audio cassettes
    - Connecticut political campaigns (44 tapes) (Box 73)